Guide to the Rice Center for Community Design + Research records, 1968-1987 UA 181
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice Center for Community Design + Research records
1968-1987
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice Center for Community Design + Research
UA 181
9 Linear Feet (9 boxes)
The collection consists of both published and unpublished records of projects undertaken by the Rice Center for Community Design + Research, subsequently the Rice Center. It also includes records of two projects of the University of Louisville which served as precursors to much of the early research completed at the Rice Center.
Biographical / Historical
Beginning in 1973, the Rice Center for Community Design + Research was an organization within the School of Architecture at Rice University. In 1978 it was expanded to the entire University, and the name was shortened to Rice Center. Its purpose was to conduct research for both public and private entities. Internally it created research projects judged beneficial to the Houston and Texas community. These independent research projects were funded by substantial foundation grants and private contributions. In approximately 1975 it was designated a National Center of Research Excellence by the Urban Mass Transit Administration and received long term support for transportation research. This collection includes the Rice Center projects that were published; additional projects took place that were not published. It also includes material created at the University of Louisville that served as examples of the kinds of research anticipated.
Donald L. Williams, the first Executive Director, became President and COO in 1978, remaining in that position until 1985 when he resigned to return to the private sector. The Center continued to operate through 1991.
Scope and Contents
The Center's publications are of four main types: technical reports, represented by detailed methodology and findings of non-proprietary projects; research summaries, which present in capsule form the results of community-oriented research Technical Reports; research profiles, which summarize economics and demographics of regions; and research briefs, which describe various office activity centers in Houston, Dallas, and San Antonio.
In addition the collection includes publications of the Center's Joint Center for Urban Mobility Research, Real Estate Markets Briefs, and occasional Center newsletters, research papers, working papers, surveys, and proposals, as well as conference reports of importance to the Center's advancement.
Included with these materials generated by the Center are records of two projects of the University of Louisville Urban Studies Center which served as precursors to much of the early research completed at the Rice Center.
Access Restrictions
This material is open for research. Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Part of the collection was separated from John Margrave's papers in July 2004. The remainder was donated by Donald L. Williams, Executive Director of the Rice Center for Community Design + Research 1972-1977 and President, COO 1978-1985. The latter materials were donated Dec. 13, 2007.
Index Terms
Subjects
Architecture; Universities and colleges
Document Types
letters (correspondence); minutes (administrative records); reports
Subjects (Persons)
Williams, Donald L.
Subjects (Corporations)
Rice University; Rice University School of Architecture
- Series I: Board materials, 1973-1985; 148077
  - Board of Directors meeting minutes, January 1973-1979, 148078 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors Manual, October 1979, 148079 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors meeting minutes, 1980, 148080 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors meeting minutes, 1981, 148081 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors meeting minutes, 1982, 148082 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors meeting minutes, 1983, 148083 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors meeting minutes, 24 October 1984, 148084 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors meeting agendas, 31 Jan. and 25 April 1985, 148085 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Series II: Internal reports and correspondence, 1972-1985; 148838
  - Executive Committee meeting records, 1973, 148086 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee meeting records, 1979, 148087 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee meeting records, 1980, 148088 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee meeting records, 1981, 148089 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee meeting records, 1982, 148090 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee meeting records, 1983, 148091 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee meeting records, 1985, 148092 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Incorportation Documents, 1972-1973, 148093 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Rice Center Updates, July 1976, February 1977, and November 1977, 214655 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, 22 Dec. 1972 - 10 Oct. 1983, 148094 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Financial Statements and Auditor's Report, 30 June 1978-1983, 148095 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Financial Reports, 1 Oct. 1980 - 15 Feb. 1985, 148096 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Operations Reports, 31 July 1979 - 31 Jan. 1985, 148097 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Development Reports, 26 Nov. 1979 - 31 Jan. 1985, 148098 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Management Briefs, 30 Sept. 1979- 31 May 1983, 148099 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Annual Plans FY 1981/82 - FY 1984, 148100 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Reports of the Development Committee, May 1972 - 22 Dec. 1972, 148101 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Introductory Report, November 1972, 148102 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The City Edges in Texas Proposal, 11 Dec 1972, 148103 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Texas Gulf Coast Program Proposal, 1 Jan. 1973, 148104 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Active Project Descriptions, 23 Jan 1973 - 31 March 1983, 148105 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Internal Accounting Control Reports, 1979-1983, 148106 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - University Presidents meeting with Woodlands Development Co. Records, 27 March 1980, 148107 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Research Summary, May 1981, 148108 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Houston Area Profile, October 1982, 148109 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Research Summary, January 1983, 148110 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Series III: Community design and research files, 1968-1987, 214438
  - University of Louisville Urban Studies Center Reports on New community Development, 1968-1970, 214656 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - University of Louisville Urban Studies Reports on new Community Development, 1968-1970, 214657 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - University of Louisville Urban Studies Center Reports on New Community Development, 1968 - 1970, 214658 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Environmental Impact Control program; 1 Dec 1969, 214659 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - The New Community and Family mobility System; June 1970, 214660 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - New Com Summary I; November 1971, 214661 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - New Com: The Psychosocial Environment II; November 1971, 214662 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - New Com: The Pysical Environment III; November 1971, 214663 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - New Com: The Enabling Elements IV; November 1971, 214664 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - New Com: Technical Supplement V; November 1971, 214665 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - New Community U.S. Office of Economic Opportunity Contract, 1969 - 1971, 214666 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Master Planning Grant Application, Louisville & Jefferson County Air Board; February 1971, 214667 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Environmental Capacities, Final Report: Urban Demonstration Corridor; February 1971. Urban Studies Center of the University of Louisville (USCUL), 214668 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Technical Appendix, Final Report: Urban Demonstration Corridor; February 1971. USCUL, 214669 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Socio-environmental Evaluation, Final Report: Urban Demonstration Corridor; February 1971. USCUL, 214670 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Airport Natural Environment Analysis Summary, October 1972. USCUL, 214671 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Aurport Natural Environment Analysis, Louisville Region, Kentucky Area Wide Analysis for the Louisville & Jefferson County Air Board; 31 December 1971. USCUL, 214672 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - A Survey of Natural Science Information and Situation in the Kentucky Portion of the Louisville Central Region, for the Louisville & Jefferson County Air Board; 31 October 1972. USCUL, 214673 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Airport Natural Environment Analysis, Louisville Region, Indiana Area-Wide Analysis for the Louisville & Jefferson County Air Board; October 1972. USCUL, 214674 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Site Evaluation Committee Meeting Plan, October 17-18, 1972, 214675 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Natural Environmental Impacts of Expanding Standiford Field, Plan E: A Report to the Louisville & Jefferson County Air Board; 24 August 1973. Arthur D. Little, Inc., Washington, D.C., 214676 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Proposed Airport Site Evaluation Methodology, Louisville & Jefferson County Air Board; 16 October 1972, 214677 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Site Evaluation, Criteria Information, Site Evaluation Committee for the Louisville & Jefferson County Airboard; 16 October 1972, 214678 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Airport Natural Environment Analysis Summary, Urban Studies Center; October 1972, 214679 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Airport Natral Environment Analysis, Micro-Analysis: Four Sites in Kentucky, for the Louisville & Jefferson County Air Board; 1 August 1973. USCUL, 214680 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Technical Memorandum, Phase I Site Evaluation, August 1973; Prepared for Louisville & Jefferson County Air Board by Schimpeler. Corradino Associates, Louisville, KY, 214681 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Technical Memorandum, Phase II Site Evaluation, January 1974; Prepared for Louisville & Jefferson County Air Board by Schimpeler. Corradino Associates, Louisville, KY, 214682 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Texas Gulf Program Survey, 2 January 1973 (RC-CD+R), 214683 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Texas Gulf Coast Program Proposal, 25 January 1973 (RC-CD+R), 214684 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Preliminary Environmental Evaluation, Kashmere Union Station for Bus Storage, Maintenance, Operating, and General Office Facilities, c. 1974 (RC-CD+R), 214685 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Program Planning for Houston Multi-service Centers, n.d. (RC-CD+R), 214686 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Austin County Jail, Preliminary Planning Program, 30 September 1973 (RC-CD+R), 214687 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Fort Bend County Jail Facilities, Preliminary Planning Program; 15 March 1974 (RC-CD+R), 214688 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Galbeston County Jail Facilities, Preliminary Planning Program; 30 April 1974 (RC-CD+R), 214689 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Proceedings of the Western States Land Commissioners' Association Annual Meeting, Lakeway Inn, Austin, TX, 28 July - 1 August 1974, 214690 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Potential for Energy Conservation in the United States: 1974 - 1978. A Report of the National Petroleum Council, 10 September 1974, 214691 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Proceedings, First Houston Technology Transfer Conference, 24-25 September 1974. Sponsored by the Houston Chamber of Commerce in Cooperation with NASA, 214692 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - A Value Capture Policy, Introduction; 1 November 1974 (RC-CD+R), 214693 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - A Value Capture Policy, Community Enhancement; 1 November 1974 (RC-CD+R), 214694 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - A Value Capture Policy, Financial; 1 November 1974 (RC-CD+R), 214695 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - A Value Capture Policy, Legal; 1 November 1974 (RC-CD+R), 214696 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - A Value Capture Policy, Community Enhancement, November 1974; Department of Transportation, Office of the Secretary, Office of University Research, Washington, DC 20590, 214697 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - A Value Capture Policy, Financial, November 1974; Department of Transportation, Office of the Secretary, Office of University Research, Washington, DC 20590, 214698 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - A Value Capture Policy, Legal, November 1974; Department of Transportation, Office of the Secretary, Office of University Research, Washington, DC 20590, 214699 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - South Main Center Association Brochure, no date, 214700 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Baylor College of Medicine Planning Report, September 1975 (RC-CD+R), 214701 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Options for a Unique Texas Place, South Main Street Area, 20 November 1975 (RC-CD+R), 214702 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Research Report 1, Texas Gulf Coast Program, January 1976 (RC-CD+R), 214703 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Research Report 1, Maps 1-8, Texas Gulf Coast Program, January 1976 (RC-CD+R), 214704 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Research Report 1 Maps 9 - 16, Texas Gulf Coast Program, January 1976 (RC-CD+R), 214705 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Executive Summary, Joint Development, Value Capture Applications, 1 January 1976 (RC-CD+R), 214706 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - ERD/76: Environmental Design Research, 1976: A Summary Report of Five Regional Environmental Design Conferences Held in the United States During June 1976 (RC-CD+R); October 1976, 214707 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - RANN2: Realizing Knowledge as a Resource: Proceedings of the Second Symposium on Research Applied to National Needs, Volume IV, Coping with Man-Made and Natural Hazards, November 1976, 214708 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Southwest Center for Urban Research, Environmental Analysis for Development Planning, Chambers County, Texas, Technical Report Volume 2: Federal Influence on Land Resources Management, 1 June 1974, 214709 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Southwest Center for Urban Research, Environmental Analysis for Development Planning, Chambers County, Texas, Technical Report Volume 3: Coastal Zone Management: A Proposed Incremental Change System for Texas, 1 June 1974, 214710 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Southwest Center for Urban Research, Environmental Analysis for Development Planning, Chambers County, Texas, Technical Report Volume 5: Applications for the Texas Coastal Zone Management Program, 1 December 1975, 214711 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Southwest Center for Urban Research, Environmental Analysis for Development Planning, Chambers County, Texas, Technical Report Volume 6: An Approach for Describing Natural Systems and for Assessing Natural Environmental Impact, March 1976, 214712 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Southwest Center for Urban Research, Environmental Analysis for Development Planning, Chambers County, Texas, Technical Report Volume 7: Environmental Analysis Case Study Applications and Selected Technical Papers, March 1976, 214713 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - City of Houston, Houston Downtown People Mover: Proposal to the Urban Mass Transit Administration, 30 June 1976, reprint 1 May 1977 and 10 August 1977, 214714 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Inside Loop 610: Froces for Change (RC-CD+R); 30 June 1976, 214715 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Program Planning Refinements for Houston Multi-service Centers: Kashmere, Magnolia, Sunnyside (RC-CD+R); 30 June 1976, 214716 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Joint Development / Value Capture: Digest of Conference Proceedings (RC-CD+R); 23 September 1976, 214717 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Critical Environmental Issues for Conoco: A Reference for Operating Managers (RC-CD+R); no date, 214718 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Downtown Traffic Analysis: Information for Houston Facility Location Decision Working Papers Number 1-6 (RC-CD+R); 29 April - 5 October 1977, 214719 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Third Ward Area Transit Needs Analysis, April 1977 (RC-CD+R), 214720 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Greenway Post Oak Transit Needs Analysis, April 1977 (RC-CD+R), 214721 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Texas Medical Center Transit Needs Analysis, April 1977 (RC-CD+R), 214722 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - User's Guide: Community Development Model, Prepared for Arabian American Oil Co., Saudi Arabian Operations (RC-CD+R); 30 September 1977, 214723 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Streetscape Improvement Program, Houston, Texas (RC-CD+R); October 1977, 214724 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Growth Options for Houston, Technical Report, Rice Center; March 1978, 214725 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Katy Freeway: Opportunities for Areawide Action, Rice Center; 30 March 1978, 214726 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - New Single Family Housing Affordability in Houston: Past, Present, and Future Trends, Rice Center; April 1978, 214727 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Technical Reports: The Delay Costs of Government Regulation in the Houston Housing Market, Rice Center; 31 May 1978, 214728 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Research Paper: The Public Costs and the Benefits of the 30 Percent Devloper Contribution Rule, Prepared for the Greater Houston Builders' Association and Houston Board of Realtors, Rice Center; June 1978, 214729 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Allen Center Terminal Project for the Joint Development Marketplace, Washington, June 25-27, 1978, Rice Center, 214730 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Downtown Fact Book: Technical Report, April 1978, Rice Center, 214731 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Downtown Transfer Facility Feasibility Evaluation July 1978, Rice Center, 214732 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Park & Ride Environmental Analysis, Stuebner-Airline, Kuykendahl, Rice Center; Summer 1978, 214733 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 1978 Update of the Transit Action Program, Rice Center; July 1978, 214734 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Westheimer Cooridor Study, Rice Center, August 1978, 214735 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Downtown Transit Mall Preliminary Evaluation, Rice Center, December 1978, 214736 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - The Cost of Delay due to Governmental Regulation in the Houston housing Market. Urban Land Institute Research Report #28, Rice Center, 1979, 214737 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - The Houston Regional Concrete Market: Past Problems and Future Projections, Rice Center; February 1979, 214738 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Research Report: Annexation and Houston, Rice Center; March 1979, 214739 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Technical Report: Socio-Economic Impact Analysis of Selected Air Pollution Controls in the Houston-Galveston Region. Prepared for Houston Area Oxidants Study, Rice Center; March 1979, 214740 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Phase One Technical Report: Economic Base Analysis for the Houston-Galveston Region, Rice Center; April 1979, 214741 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Research Paper: A Case Study of Access and Amenity Features at Five Houston Area Office Locations. Prepared for Century Devlopment Corporation, Rice Center; March 1980, 214742 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Joint Development Report (Department of Transportation Urban mass Transportation Administration), Rice Center; June 1979, 214743 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Amoco Production Company: An Analysis of Three Office Location Alternatives, Rice Center; August 1979, 214744 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Sabine Pass Economic Base Analysis. Prepared for the City of Port Arthur, Rice Center; November 1979, 214745 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Research Related to the Public Works Department, City of Houston. Part One: Technical Memorandum, 1 December 1979; Part Two: Memorandum, 26 March 1981. Rice Center, 214746 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Hughes Tool Company: An Analysis of Corporate Office Locations, Rice Center; 4 January 1980, 214747 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Sabine Pass Environmental Analysis. Prepared for the City of Port Arthur, Rice Center; January 1980, 214748 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Forecast 2000: Population and Employment in the Houston-Galveston Region, Phase Two. Final Report, Rice Center; February 1980, 214749 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - St. Joseph Hospital Market Survey and Site Research Study, Rice Center; April 1980, 214750 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - An Analysis of Houston Area Floods, Volume 1, Technical Analysis, Rice Center; June 1980, 214751 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Results of Surveys on Measures for Improving Transportation in Houston. Prepared for the Atlantic Richfield Foundation, Rice Center, August 1980, 214752 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Houston International Exposition, Rice Center; c. Fall 1980, 214753 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Alternative Actions for Achieving Energy Savings in the Transportation Sector, Rice Center; November 1980, 214754 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - The Impact of a Fuel Shortage on the Houston Transportation System, Interim Report, Rice Center; December 1980, 214755 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Sales Projections: Turner Collie & Braden, Inc., Firm and Market Category. Rice Center; 12 January 1981, 214756 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Houston Initiatives, Phase One Report, Rice Center; June 1981, 214757 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Analysis of Three Alternative Corridsors for Prospective Location of Penzoil Research Facility. Rice Center; 2 June 1981, 214758 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Dallas/Ft. Worth Marketplace Study. Turner Collie & Brade, Inc., Dallas Office. Rice Center; September 1981, 214759 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Westem Colorado Engineering Markets, draft. Prepared for Turner Collie & Braden, Inc. Rice Center; end of 1981, 214760 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Prudential Southwest Home Office, Phase II Report, draft. Rice Center; 1982, 214761 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Redevelopment Scenarios for the North End of the Houston CBD, Rice Center; April 1982, 214762 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Clear Lake City Park & Ride Analysis. Prepared for Barry M. Goodman Associates, Inc. Rice Center; August 1982, 214763 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Harris County Office Demand Forecasts, Rice Center; October 1982, 214764 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - An Implementation for a Houston Downtown Organization, Rice Center; October 1982, 214765 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - C.R.H. Associates, Market Research for the Houston Office: Competition, Rice Center; January 1983, 214831 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Future Public Services Delivery and Local Governance in the Woodlands. Prepared for the Woodlands Community Association, Rice Center; 22 April 1983, 214832 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Texas Energy Development Fund, Onshore Impacts of Offshore Oil and Gas Activities: Coastal Data Inventory, Volume I. Texas Energy and Natural Resources Advisory Council, Rice Center; January 1983, 214833 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Texas Energy Development Fund, Onshore Impacts of offshore Oil and Gas Activiteies: Coastal Impact Assessment, Volume IIA. Texas Energy and Natural Resources Advisory Council, Rice Center; February 1983, 214834 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Texas Energy Development Fund, Onshore Impacts of Offshore Oil and Gas Activities: Coastal Impact Assessment, Volume IIB, Appendix B. Texas Energy and Natural Resources Advisory Council, Rice Center; February 1983, 214835 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Texas Energy Development Fund, Oil & Gas Activities: Issues and Implications, Volume III. Texas Energy and Natural Resources Advisory Council, Rice Center; March 1983, 214836 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Summary, Onshore Impacts of Offshore Oil and Gas Activities. Prepared for Texas Energy and Natural Resources Advisory Council, Rice Center; March 1983, 214837 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Houston Issues Definition Project 82 - 2001, Research Task Outputs, Rice Center; 15 November 1982 - 7 December 1982, 214838 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Allen Parkway Village / Fourth Ward. Prepared for the Housing Authority of the City of Houston. Technical Report with the Assistance of the Rice Center; September 1983, 214839 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Growth Cities Data, Rice Center; October 1983, 214840 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Growth Cities: Los Angeles, Dallas, Atlanta, Phoenix, Tampa, Denver. Rice Center; February 1984, 214841 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Houston/Independent Research program, Population, and Housing Profiles, Zip Codes, and Census Tracts Selected 1980 Census Results. Rice Center; c. 1983, 214842 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Project G Graphics and Narrative Analysis to Evaluate Alternative Locations for a Future Office Complex for Getty Oil Company's Houston Division and Dsitrict Office. Rice Center; c. 1984, 214843 (Box 9, Folder 13)